

DUY LAN LE

STUDENT | SOUTHEAST COMMUNITY COLLEGE

OBJECTIVE

I always want to learn about new things. I love solving problems and I think I'm pretty good at it. I want to be a better version of myself, and I also want to earn a lot of money.

SKILLS

I'm good at problems solving and I learned a little bit about programing especially with Python. I have a few project to test myself like: Sudoku solver, and a trading bot using robinhood and yahoo finance API.

I have experience in using Adobe Photoshop and Premier.

I built a few website using Bootstrap, sweetalert, etc.

EXPERIENCE

VIDEO EDITOR • COMPANY - OVERWATCH X • 2016 – 2018

I have a full time job at Overwatch X at a video editor. In here, I learned a lot of experiences about leadership and teambuilding, I learned how to communicate when working with a team. This job also guides me how to learn something completely new to me through in the internet.

KITCHEN ASSISTANT • RESTAURANT - PHO 14 • 2018 - 2020
This is the first job when I landed on US, I learn a lot of management skill here. Practicing cooking with me is a good experience.

WEB DEVELOPER • CODER FOUNDRY • 2021 – CURRENT

Coder Foundry is a great company and school; I have learned a lot of knowledge about web development, C#, Xamarin, and mobile development in here. My colleges are very friendly and cooperated.

EDUCATION

GRADUATED • 2015 • VO TRUONG TOAN HIGH SCHOOL

I graduated from my high school in 2015 with 3.0 GPA.

CURRENTLY • 2020 • SOUTHEAST COMMUNITY COLLEGE

I'm currently enrolling in Southeast Community College in Academic Transfer in Lincoln, Nebraska. My current GPA is 3.554.







